autologic.com 2017-06-28

# Privacy Policy

## Autologic Diagnostics Group Limited Privacy Policy 

Autologic Diagnostics Group Limited, and all its subsidiaries, are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our customers and visitors to our website. This policy demonstrates our commitment to your privacy, and explains how we will treat your Personal Information.

Personal Information is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Our privacy policy is intended to give you a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personal Information.

### What types of information do we collect?

When ordering or registering on our website, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register on our website, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, open a support ticket, provide us with feedback on our products or services, or otherwise enter information on our website.

### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To improve our website in order to serve you better.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products.
  * To follow up with you after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries).

### How do we protect your information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. We use regular Malware Scanning.

Your Personal Information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order or otherwise enters, submits, or accesses their information, in order to maintain the safety of your Personal Information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

### Cookies

When you visit our website we may use cookies. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since each browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.

We honor Do Not Track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personal Information. Our site does not allow third-party behavioural tracking.

### Third-party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

### Google

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

### Fair Information Practices

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

  * We will notify you via email within 7 business days.
  * We will notify all users via in-site notification within 7 business days.

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

### CAN SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
  * Send you additional information related to your product and/or service.
  * Market / send emails to our mailing list / clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

### Preferences

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at info@autologic.com or follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence. You can change your personal information by logging in to your account. You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes on our Privacy Policy Page.

### Contacting Us

If you have any questions please contact us using the information below.

Autologic House,  
London Road,  
Oxford,  
Oxfordshire OX33 1JH  
United Kingdom

+44 1865 870 060
